floraqueen.com 2015-10-02

# Privacy and Legal - Flower deliveries

With FloraQueen you are always safe and secure. We value and respect all our clients and treat every detail with the greatest of care.

Company Information

FloraQueen Flowering the World S.L (FloraQueen). is registered in the Mercantile Registry of Barcelona, Volume 36.886, Folio 206, Page B 290474. Fiscal identification code B-63609051.  
Address: C/Frederic Mompou, 3 7ºB, 08960 Sant Just Desvern (Barcelona) - Spain Contact us at: info[at]FloraQueen.com.

We would like to remind you that these are the general terms and conditions relating to our websites, and their services, features, contents and applications.

Copyright Information

Copyright © 2002 FloraQueen Flowering the World S.L. All Rights Reserved.

Trademarks

The FloraQueen logo, all taglines, are trademarks or copyrights of FloraQueen Any reproduction or distribution of FloraQueen trademarks, copyrights, software, or Web site content without the written permission of FloraQueen is strictly prohibited. All other products and company names are trademarks or copyrights of their respective owners.

Privacy Policy

Information Collected by FloraQueen when you visit the FloraQueen site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site usage information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

Please note that we reserve the right to link the personal information you provide on our different websites and through FloraQueen’s current and future mobile applications.

Personal Information You Choose to Provide

If you submit information as a result of a request for more information from FloraQueen, FloraQueen will not share the submitted information with any third parties. Our lists are private and are not sold or exchanged with outside entities. FloraQueen may choose to share the submitted information with strategic partners for the purpose of helping us to provide our solutions.

Sharing Information with Strategic Partners

We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information.

Web Site Use Information

Like other commercial Web sites, the FloraQueen Web site utilizes Web server logs to collect information regarding how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just prior to and after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an Individual, and your individual usage patterns cannot be retrieved.

What are Cookies?

Cookies are tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit our website. Thanks to the information stored in cookies, your preferences are remembered when you return to the website and you thereby enjoy a better browsing experience.

If you prefer to disable cookies, you can do so by modifying your browser settings. However, this may prevent some parts of our site from functioning properly, as they play an essential role in the provision of our services.

And what if I Prefer to Block Cookies?

If you do not enable cookies on your computer, access may be denied to some parts of the site and your experience on our website may be limited in some areas:

  * When you log into your account
  * Content on the website customised to your preferences
  * A record of your tastes and interests on your next visit

Why is it Better to Allow Cookies?

Because you will be able to enjoy many of the site’s essential functions, enhancing your experience on our website. For instance, in the customised recommendations according to your tastes, access to exclusive areas such as your account, keeping a record of the products stored in your basket and improving security by preventing fraudulent activities.

How do I Configure Cookies?

Accepting cookies optimises browsing; therefore, most browsers are already configured to accept them by default. However, if you prefer, you can change this setting. Please see the details in your browser settings.

Use of Web Site Information

Content included in this site may be used by you solely for personal, informational, and/or non-commercial purposes and may not be modified or altered in any way. Except as expressly provided herein, you may not use, download, upload, copy, print, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, post, transmit or distribute any information from this Web site in whole or in part without prior written consent from FloraQueen.

Employee Access, Training and Expectations

Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection and privacy of customer and Web site visitor information.

Legally Disclosure of Information

We may disclose your information when legally compelled to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.

External Links

This Web site may contain hyperlinks to Web sites controlled by parties other than FloraQueen. FloraQueen is not responsible for and does not endorse or accept any responsibility over the content or use of these Web sites. We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Consent

By using the FloraQueen’s Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. If you do not agree with these changes, your sole recourse is to discontinue use of the Web site.

Notice of New Services and Changes

Occasionally, FloraQueen may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers that you may find of interest. You will be given the opportunity to opt out of receiving these notices by clicking on a response box when you receive such notices or by sending us an email request at info@floraqueen.com. If you have any questions regarding FloraQueen policy please email us at info@floraqueen.com.

Smiles Guaranteed

>  **Zoran (Australia)**
> 
> Thank you thank you thank you. I Don't have words to thank you how everything went perfect. even with my late change for delivery time you have made me and the person I love so much very happy. Please pass my thanks to your team as well as to florist in Croatia. Thank you all.

Rated 4.2 out of 5 by 6215 reviewers 

  * Halloween Flowers 2015-10-31T00:01 2015-10-31T23:59
  * Neighbour Day 2015-11-15T00:01 2015-11-28T23:59
  * Thanksgiving International flowers 2015-11-27T00:01 2015-11-27T23:59
  * International Christmas Flower Delivery 2015-12-24T00:01 2015-12-26T23:59

Amazing tools and a huge media library

Premium Flowers and Gifts

A new opportunity with a wide range of benefits and new orders from new clients

Start receiving orders now
